嘿 杰克 那些架子不会上去
Hey, Jack, those racks don't go up there.
-你是什么意思? -他们进入停车场
- What do you mean? -They go in the parking lot.
有蓝色塑料的那些在那里
The ones with blue plastic go up there.
啊 好的 嘿 抱歉 我没有意识到
Ah, okay, hey, sorry, I didn't realize.
别担心 你被解雇了
Don't worry, you're fired.
顺便说一句 我们今晚将会想你
By the way, we're gonna miss you tonight.
现在不要感到伤心
Don't get sentimental on me now.
但是不一样
But it won't be the same.
闭嘴
Shut up.
-我们做到了罗曼 他们完成了
-We did it. -Roman, have they finished
在6楼的框架?
the frame on the 6th floor yet?
是的 并在七楼的框架
Yes, and the framing on the 7th floor
应在接下来的三个小时内完成
should be done within the next three hours.
地下室辐条的问题?
The problem with the spokes in the basement?
那么我们也解决了这个问题
Well, we solved that problem, too.
如果明天早上启动外壳
And if you start the enclosures tomorrow morning,
我们应该提前一天
we should be one day ahead of schedule.
所以回家
So go home.
为什么?
Why?
那你的家人今天到了 对吧?
Well, your family's arriving today, right?
是的 但是直到深夜才飞
Yeah, but they're not flying in until later in the night.
所以继续 回家
So go on, go home.
为他们准备一切 这是一个很大的一天
Get everything ready for them, it's a big day.
我为他们准备了一切
I have everything ready for them.
我的意思是 我整个房子都装满了
I mean, I have the whole house decked out.
马特 你不会相信的欢迎招牌 一切
Matt, you wouldn't believe it. Welcome signs, everything.
嗯 你最好早点离开 万一有交通
Well, you're better off leaving early in case there's traffic.
-好吧 也许你是对的 -当然 我是对的！
-Well, maybe you're right. -Of course, I'm right!
现在继续 离开这里 明天休息
Now go on, get out of here and take tomorrow off.
花一些时间与你的女儿
Spend some time with your daughter.
基督 你要成为祖父
Christ, you're gonna be a grandfather.
继续
Go on.
明天不要来 我认识你
Do not come tomorrow, i know you.
这是 wsny和wsny hd哥伦布
This is wsny and wsny hd Columbus.
795年的圣诞快乐！
Merry Christmas from 795!
乘客琼斯 请在门口查看 票务代理商
Passenger Jones, please see the ticketing agents at the gate.
请不要 将您的行李无人值守
Please do not leave your luggage unattended,
行李无人值守 可能会被删除...
luggage left unattended  may be removed...
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
嗨 老兄！对不起 对不起 先生
Hey, man! Excuse me, excuse me, sir.
你是一个很好的舞者
You're a good dancer.
嗨 -你好先生
-Hi. -Hello, sir.
是的 我正在等待飞行
Yeah, I'm waiting for a flight
它说这是延迟 但没有eta
and it says it's delayed, but there's no eta.
它是斧头1-12 -Ax 1-12?
-It's ax 1-12. -Ax 1-12?
是的 从基辅起飞 在法兰克福和纽约下车
Yeah taking off from Kiev, with a lay over in Frankfurt and New York.
-好的? -Ax 1-12?
-Okay? -Ax 1-12?
没错 是的 我确信我没有写错了
That's right, yeah, I'm sure i didn't write it down wrong.
请跟我来
Please come with me.
-谢谢 -小心 先生
-Thank you. -Take care, sir.
-你能告诉我你的名字吗?罗曼 罗马melnyk
-Can you tell me your name? -Roman, Roman melnyk.
-我看到你的身份证 梅尔尼克先生? -当然
-Can I see your ID, Mr. melnyk? -Sure.
我的妻子和女儿到了
My wife and daughter are arriving.
我知道他们的所有文件都是有序的
I know all their papers are in order.
我们有一个律师 所以不应该有任何问题
We have a lawyer so there shouldn't be any problems.
我确定没有 ...这周围
I'm sure there wasn't. ...Around here.
你能坐在这里吗?
Could you just have a seat in here, please?
好的谢谢
Okay, thanks.
我可以给你任何饮水吗?
Can I get you any water, anything to drink?
不 不 谢谢谢谢飞机早点到达了吗?
No, no, thank you. Thank you. Did the plane arrive early?
我的意思是他们在这里吗?
I mean, are they here already?
我没有所有的信息 所以我不想
I don't have all the information so I don't want to
告诉你任何可能不真实的事情
tell you anything that might not be true.
有人会对你说话
Somebody will be right in to speak with you.
好的
Okay.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你什么意思?他们在哪?
What do you mean? Where are they?
我需要看到他们！
I need to see them!
罗马melnyk
Roman melnyk.
我的家人在哪里
Where's my family?
嗯...我的名字是夏娃桑德斯 我是联系人之一
Um... my name is Eve Sanders and I'm one of the contact people
由机场管理处指定
assigned by the airport management office.
我需要你仔细听我说的话
I need you to listen very carefully to what I have to say.
你的妻子和女儿正在旅行的飞机
The airplane that your wife and daughter were traveling in
遇到了一个非常不幸的事故
has had a very unfortunate accident.
还没有正式确认
There's still no official confirmation,
但是我们需要牢记这种事故
but we need to keep in mind that with this type of accident
我们不可能找到任何幸存者
it's unlikely that we'll find any survivors.
这是任何人都会收到的最糟糕的消息
It is the worst news that anyone will ever receive.
她怀孕了
She was pregnant.
奥莉娜去接她 把她带回来
Olena went to pick her up, to bring her back.
这个地址和联系电话是否正确?
Are this address and contact number correct?
还有其他的家庭成员应该告诉我们吗?
And are there any other family members we should inform?
-不是吗?
-No -nobody?
不在这里还是在你的原籍国?
Not here or in your country of origin?
家庭支援中心已在附近的酒店设立
The family support center has been set up at a hotel nearby.
你可以获得医疗和心理
You'll have access to medical and psychological
治疗和社会服务
treatments and social services.
这也是您将在任何新闻的更新
That's also where you'll be updated on any news that comes in.
如果你宁愿独自一人 也可以在那里做
If you'd rather be alone, you can do that there, too.
没有
No.
我建议你明天去家庭支援中心
I would recommend that you go to the family support center tomorrow,
当你感觉更强壮
when you're feeling stronger.
你也有我的电子邮件 手机
You also have my email, cell phone
和我部门的电话号码
and my department's phone number.
请不要犹豫 打电话给我
Please don't hesitate to call me.
-是 -很好
-Yes. -Very well.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait...
-你和水暖工谈话吗? -闭嘴！
-Did you talk to the plumber? -Shut up!
你没有?
You didn't?
地下室里有一个厕所仍然卡住
There's a toilet in the basement still jammed.
呃 我们要醒来撒母耳记上
Shh, we're gonna wake up Samuel.
-我爱你 -我爱你
-I love you. -I love you.
他出来了 -你知道 当我还是个孩子的时候
-He's out. -You know, when I was a kid,
我有这个小的熊 他的名字是以实玛利
I had this little stuffed bear, his name was ishmael.
-Ishmael?是啊
-Ishmael? -Yeah.
这是一只熊的奇怪名字
That's a weird name for a bear.
当我们去旅行时 我总是不得不把他带走
And when we took trips i always had to take him with me
或者我不能睡觉
or I wouldn't be able to sleep.
这一直很久以后
This went on 'til much, much later.
多久以后
How much later?
“你是24岁? “你跟我见过吗?
'Til you were 24? 'Til you met me?
我不知道
I don't know.
你总是说没有我 你不能睡觉
You always say that you can't sleep without me.
对 是真的我只是不知道该怎么想
Yeah, that's true. I just don't know what to think.
-什么?我所有的都是你吗?
-What? -Is that all I am to you?
一些糟糕的替补为以实玛利?
Some lousy substitute for ishmael?
呃 以实玛利的替补是一个很大的荣幸
Hey, being ishmael's substitute is a big honor.
我会为以实玛利做任何事情
I'd do anything for ishmael.
你有跟以实玛利做爱吗?
Did you have sex with ishmael?
我迟到了工作
I'm late for work.
L-r 5-7-4 右转在bravo 2-6
L-r, 5-7-4, turn right on bravo 2-6.
嗨 嘿！ -晚间
-Hey, hey! -Evening.
两口气 你会跑到浴室
Two sips of that and you'll be running for the bathroom.
是啊我在浴室里会记得你
Yeah? I'll remember you while I'm in the bathroom,
如果那是你想要的
if that's what you want.
不 不 谢谢 我不会把它从我的头
No, no, thanks, I'm not gonna get that out of my head.
不 只要记住谁警告你
No, just remember who warned you.
-我们有什么? -我们得点零食
-What do we got? -Well, we got to get a snack.
你想要什么?不 我很好谢了 兄弟
-You want anything? -No, I'm good. Thanks, brother.
我登上了最后一个 甲板上没什么
I landed the last one and there's nothing on deck.
加拿大8-2-6允许 爬升并维持3-3-0-0
Canada 8-2-6. Permission to climb and maintain 3-3-0-0.
加拿大8-2-6  爬升并维持3-3-0级
Canada 8-2-6, climb and maintain level 3-3-0.
谢谢哥伦布  晚安
Thank you, Columbus, and good night.
晚间
Evening.
Na 1-9-7-9降至飞行3-0级
Na 1-9-7-9 descend to flight level 3-0.
Na 1-9-7-9 降序...
Na 1-9-7-9, descending...
嘿 你在做什么?
Hey, what are you doing?
在电话线上进行一些维护
Doing some maintenance on the telephone lines.
要把它放在安全模式下 所以它应该可以正常工作
Gonna put it on security mode so it should work fine.
有时信号有点软弱只需五六分钟
Sometimes the signal's a little weak. Just five or six minutes.
塔c 晚上好
Tower c, good evening.
这是对于cmh的斧头1-12
This is ax 1-12 down for cmh,
请求许可 下降到10,000英尺
requesting permission to descend to 10,000 feet.
罗杰斧1-1-2 等待确认下降
Roger ax 1-1-2, wait for confirmation on that descend.
复制
Copy that.
嗨 雅各布 托马斯走了出来?
Hey, Jacob, Thomas stepped out?
这是怎么回事?
What's up?
我们有一个意想不到的飞行 如1-3-5
We got an unexpected flight, ef 1-3-5.
由于恶劣的天气不得不改变路线
Had to change its route because of the bad weather.
为匹兹堡打来 -好的 谢谢
-Headed for Pittsburgh. -Alright, thanks.
去吧 给那个塔头
Go ahead and give that tower the heads up.
请与我联系匹兹堡机场
Connect me with Pittsburgh airport, please.
你好?
Hello?
斧头1-1-2允许下降到飞行高度1-0谢谢
Ax 1-1-2 permission to descend to flight level 1-0. Thank you.
复制谢谢  降至10,000英尺
Copy that. Thank you, descending to 10,000 feet.
Cmh 这是dh 6-1-6 你复制吗?
Cmh, this is dh 6-1-6, do you copy?
空客ef 1-3-5 这是塔c
Airbus ef 1-3-5, this is tower c.
Ef 1-3-5 晚上好
Ef 1-3-5, good evening.
我在这里的电话线有问题 我不能
I'm having a problem with the phone lines here and I can't
与匹兹堡联系
get in touch with Pittsburgh.
Cmh 这是dh 6-1-6
Cmh, this is dh 6-1-6.
我们正在从 发出警告 告诉我们下降
We're getting a warning from our tcas telling us to descend.
我重复一遍 tcas告诉我们我们下降 你复制吗?
I repeat, the tcas is telling us to descend, do you copy?
塔 这是dh 6-1-6 你复制吗?
Tower, this is dh 6-1-6, do you copy?
空客ef 1-3-5 直接联系机场
Airbus ef 1-3-5, contact airport directly.
我重复一遍 直接联系匹兹堡机场
I repeat, contact Pittsburgh airport directly.
不是问题 我们将直接与匹兹堡直接联系
Not a problem cmh, we'll contact Pittsburgh directly, over.
塔 这是  dh 6-1-6 你复制吗?
Tower, this is  dh 6-1-6, do you copy?
斧1-1-2 下降并保持飞行等级6-0
Ax 1-1-2, descend and maintain flight level 6-0.
下降到6000英尺 你复制吗?
Descend to 6,000 feet, do you copy?
斧头1-12 下降到6000英尺
Ax 1-12, descending to 6,000 feet.
Tower 我们没有 听到您的确认
Tower, we've not heard confirmation from you,
但是 我们将继续 下降到6000英尺
but we're gonna go ahead and descend to 6,000 feet.
这个恶心的手机！
This goddamned phone!
Ef 1-3-5 我们与机场交谈
Ef 1-3-5, we talked to the airport.
一切顺利 跑道确认
Everything's in order.  Runway confirmed.
Ef 1-3-5 这是塔c 复制
Ef 1-3-5, this is tower c, copy that.
斧1-1-2 斧1-1-2！
Ax 1-1-2, ax 1-1-2!
斧1-1-2！你复制吗
Ax 1-1-2! Do you copy?
斧1-1-2 你复制吗?
Ax 1-1-2, do you copy?
斧1-1-2！
Ax 1-1-2!
嗨 杰克 有个座位
Hey, Jake, have a seat.
两架飞机在高空空中相撞
Two planes collided in the air at high altitude.
显然 在18号以西几英里的一个山谷里有两架飞机的残骸
Apparently, there's wreckage from both planes in a valley several miles west of the 18.
任何人都不可能幸免于难
It's unlikely anybody survived.
多少死?
How many dead?
我们不知道
We don't know.
这些飞机有多少人?
How many people were on those planes?
我们不知道 杰克
We don't know, Jake.
哦 我的上帝 有多少人死了?
Oh, my god, how many people are dead?
杰克 听我说
Jake, listen to me.
杰克 杰克听我说我们不知道发生了什么
Jake, Jake listen to me. We don't know what happened.
没有人指责你什么
No one's accusing you of anything.
我什么也没做！我们明白了 杰克
-I didn't do anything! -We understand, Jake.
没有人在说你做了什么
No one is saying you did anything.
我们试图找出发生了什么事
We're trying to find out what happened.
我们需要你把它保持在一起 因为我们必须弄清楚这一点
We need you to keep it together because we gotta figure this out.
你听到我吗 杰克?
Do you hear me, Jake?
没有人指责你什么
No one's accusing you of anything.
我们正在做一个调查...
We're just doing an investigation...
跟我说 杰克 -...我们需要你的帮助
-Listen to me, Jake. -...We need your help.
保持在一起很重要吗?
It's very important you keep it together, alright?
谢谢
Thank you.
我们再来一遍一遍一步一步 好吗?
Let's go over it all again. Step by step, all right?
你在22:05到达控制室
You arrived at the control room at 22:05.
你坐在你的车站 约22:20
You sat at your station. At approximately 22:20
您走出了 一杯咖啡
you stepped out  for a cup of coffee.
五分钟后你回来了
You came back  five minutes later.
22:25托马斯告诉你他将要休息一下
At 22:25 Thomas told you he was gonna take a break
他离开了他的车站
and he left his station.
22:30飞行ax-112
At 22:30 flight ax-112
请求许可 下降到10,000英尺
requested permission to descend to 10,000 feet.
在22:33 两名技术人员进入控制室
At 22:33, two technicians entered the control room
在电话线上进行一些维护工作
to do some maintenance work on the phone lines.
你去了托马斯 处理其他飞机
You went to Thomas' station to process the other planes.
您打电话给匹兹堡 但 电话线路无法使用
You called Pittsburgh, but the phone line wasn't working.
同时 航班ax-112 确认其新高度
Meanwhile, flight ax-112 confirms its new altitude.
我会成为一个迟到的撒母耳晚点  你能打电话给我吗?
I'm gonna be a little late picking up Samuel.  Can you call me?
我的妹妹刚刚打电话 她 在收音机上听到某些东西
My sister just called and she heard something on the radio.
你可以打电话给我吗? 杰克 你能打电话吗?
Can you call me, please? Jake, can you call?
杰克 请给我回电话
Jake, call me back, please!
在22:45 你联系空中客车公司
At 22:45 you contact the airbus
并告诉它直接与机场进行沟通
and tell it to communicate directly with the airport.
没有你的耳机 你从来没有听说过飞行dh-616
Without your headphones you never heard flight dh-616
提醒您 即将降临
alerting you it was about to descend.
杰克杰克
Jake. Jake.
别跟任何人说话 好吗?
Don't speak to anyone, okay?
不要接电话 不要离开家 不要去任何地方
Don't answer your phone, don't leave the house, don't go anywhere.
我们明天再说一遍那么清楚吗
We'll speak again tomorrow. Is that clear?
杰克
Jake.
坚强 伙计
Be strong, buddy.
两架飞机在空中相撞
The two planes collided in the air
超过8,000英尺由于 尚未确定的原因
at more than 8,000 feet for reasons that have not yet been determined.
家庭成员 来到现场
Family members are  coming to the scene,
试图获得他们可以获得的任何 信息
trying to get any information that they can.
...乘客在船上  包括船员
...passengers were on board, including the crew.
175美国公民   38德语 37俄语  18法语
175 American citizens,  38 German, 37 Russian,  18 French,
两个乌克兰语和一个西班牙语
two Ukrainian and one Spanish.
涉及的两家航空公司 已发布联合声明
The two airlines involved have released a joint statement
对事故感到遗憾  确保他们已经
regretting the accident and assuring that they are already
与调查员完全合作
fully cooperating  with investigators
为了澄清 发生了什么
in order to clarify  what happened.
六人在你身边报道
Six on your side reporting,
yolanda哈里斯现在加入我们
yolanda Harris joining us now,
生活在现场 的崩溃约兰达?
live from the scene  of the crash. Yolanda?
我们住在不幸事故的 现场
We're live on the scene of the tragic accident.
是啊
Yeah?
先生 melnyk 这是夏娃桑德斯
Mr. melnyk, it's Eve Sanders.
我们昨天说了话
We spoke yesterday.
你今天感觉如何?
How are you feeling today?
精细
Fine.
你能睡觉吗?
Were you able to sleep?
-你休息了吗? -是的
-Have you rested at all? -Yes.
好就像我说的那样 我认为 如果你来 这可能会有帮助
Good. Like I said, I think it might help if you come
到家庭支援中心
to the family support center.
试图找到任何证据...
Trying to find any evidence...
在Hazmat船员区域内 消防和警察正在现场
In the area Hazmat crews, fire and police are on the scene.
Hazmat船员 和...有 穿过碎片...
The Hazmat crews and the... there are going through the debris...
嗨 你来帮忙搜索吗? -是
-Hi, are you here to help with the search? -Yes.
-你是否是任何受害者的亲戚或朋友? -没有
-Are you a relative or friend of any of the victims? -No.
好的 我可以看一些ID吗?
Alright, can I see some ID please?
好 当然
Yeah, sure.
福克斯先生 你有过类似的情况吗?
Alright Mr. fox, have you ever been in a similar situation?
曾经帮助过其他事故还是与受害者合作?
Ever helped out with other accidents or worked with victims before?
-是 -好的 好 给我一个帮忙
-Yes. -Alright, good, do me a favor,
仔细阅读并填写
read that thoroughly and fill it out.
等一下卡车 我会在一会儿结束
Go wait by the truck, I'll be over in a minute.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 你跟他在一起吗?
Yeah, hi, are you with him?
是啊可以看一些ID吗?
-Yeah. -Can I see some ID please?
好的 好的 给我一个帮助 加入你的朋友
Okay, good, do me a favor, join your buddy.
阅读并填写过卡车
Read that and fill it out. Go over by the truck,
我会在一分钟后带你的设备
I'll bring over your equipment in a minute.
Nadiya！
Nadiya!
纳迪亚
Nadiya.
Nadiya！
Nadiya!
奥莉娜...纳迪亚
Olena... nadiya.
甜心
Sweetie.
你知道你不能一个人在这里出去
You know you're not allowed to be out here all alone.
-你爸爸在哪里? -我不知道
-Where's your dad? -I don't know,
我今天早上没见过他
I haven't seen him since this morning.
来吧 他在里面吗
Come on, is he inside?
嘿 男人起床！
Hey, man, get up!
来吧 男人 别让我再打电话给我们 让我们走吧
Come on, man, don't make me call the cops again, let's go.
对不起 男人 但每次花费时间
I'm sorry, man, but every time you spend
晚上在这里 我遇到麻烦
the night out here, i get in trouble.
所以我们走吧 我们走吧
So let's go, let's go.
可能 fr ating fr ating fr for for for
It will probably be frustrating to look for one person to blame,
因为发生的事情比这更复杂
because what happened was much more complicated than that.
爸爸?
Daddy?
塞缪尔
Samuel.
你在那做什么?
What are you doing there?
只看电视 我睡不着
Just watching TV, i can't sleep.
你不可以睡觉吗
Can you not sleep either?
我不困我饿了
I'm not sleepy. I'm hungry.
我们来吃早餐
Let's make breakfast.
你知道吗我也饿了
You know... I'm hungry, too.
来吧
Come on.
谁是人民
Who were the people
直接参与我们刚刚描述的事件
directly involved in the events we have just described?
让我们开始 与控制室
Let's start  with the control room.
Jake bonanos 和Thomas fichman
Jake bonanos  and Thomas fichman.
从黑盒子分析 所有信息 后
After analyzing  all the information  from the black boxes,
所涉及的人的证词
testimonies from  the people involved,
证据在网站 和所有其他数据中找到
evidence found on the sites and all the other data
提供给新闻界
made available to the press,
我们可以到达 得出一些结论...
we can arrive  at some conclusions...
闻
Smell.
嗯...绿色辣椒 醋 大蒜 百里香
Mm... green chilies, vinegar, garlic, thyme.
我爱麝香草
I love thyme.
首先 只有一个空中交通管制员
First, there was only one air traffic controller
在控制室 管理空域
in the control room  managing the airspace.
杰克！
Jake!
我以为我们同意了 没有消息
I thought we agreed, no news.
-早上好 妈妈 -早安 克里斯蒂娜
-Good morning, mommy. -Good morning, Christina.
-早点啊-你饿了吗?
-So early, huh? -Are you hungry?
好的
Okay.
好吧 挖
Alright, dig in.
它是生的-嘿 你在做什么?
-It's raw. -Hey, what are you doing?
它是生的！ -克里斯蒂娜 你在干嘛?
-It's raw! -Christina, what are you doing?
小心 放手 -Christina！
-Jake, let go. -Christina!
小心 放手 -你在做什么?
-Jake, let go. -What are you doing?
-杰克 放手吧！ -可恶！
-Let... Jake, let go! -Goddammit!
没关系 我们只是吐了 没关系
It's okay we just spilled it, it's okay.
现在停止了
This stops now.
你可以做到这一点 但你必须
You can do this however you have to,
但你不会对他做的 好吗?
but you don't get to do it to him, okay?
做什么?我们正在做早餐
Do what? We're making breakfast.
来吧 回到床上
Come on, back to bed.
-来吧 -停止...
-Come on. -Stop...
你停下来克里斯蒂娜 回到这里！
You stop! Christina, get back over here!
哦 我不喜欢 你录音我！
Oh, I don't like  you recording me!
这是什么?
What is this?
妈妈 我喜欢它
Mama, I love it.
谢谢 我爱你
Thank you, I love you.
梅尔尼克先生?
Mr. melnyk?
我叫Tessa corbett 我是一名记者
My name is Tessa corbett, I'm a journalist.
我知道你在那里
I know you're in there.
我不想打扰你 我刚刚来了 因为我想要的
I don't want to bother you, i just came 'cause I wanted to
与你分享我的一些文章
share some of my articles with you.
我正在写一本关于事故的书
I'm writing a book about the accident
我想问几个问题
and I'd like to ask you a few questions.
你会看到我的文章 我试图忠实和尊重事实
You'll see from my articles that I'm trying to be faithful and respectful to the facts.
看看 如果你有机会
Take a look if you get a chance.
我会回来看看你的想法
I'll come back and see what you think.
罗马你没有回答我的电话
Roman. You haven't answered my calls for days,
我以为我会停下来
I thought I'd stop by.
哦 对不起 我的房子现在不能呈现
Oh, I'm sorry, but my house isn't presentable right now.
你还没有看到我的
You haven't seen mine.
嘿 我的妻子做了肉丸 她坚持要我带一些
Hey, my wife made meatballs and she insisted that I bring you some.
她用蘑菇把它们弄得很棒
She makes them with mushrooms, they're awesome.
-那么工作怎么样? -老了
-So, how is work? -Same old.
如果没有你 一切都会慢一些
Everything goes a little more slowly without you there.
嘿 我不是什么意思
Hey, I don't mean anything by that.
你准备好回来了
You come back whenever you're ready.
你好吗?
So, how are you?
你感觉好点了吗
Are you feeling any better?
没有
No.
是的 更好
Yes, better.
更好 只是...
Better, it's just...
我需要在这里组织
I need to get organized around here.
你知道吗 我需要绑起来
You know, I need to tie up loose ends.
当然
Sure.
我需要重新上班
And I need to get back to work.
我只需要一点时间安顿回来
I just need a little time to settle back in.
嗯 没有匆忙 罗马
Well, there's no hurry, Roman.
也许我应该在公墓里花更少的时间
Maybe I should spend less time at the cemetery.
唯一的事情是 纳迪亚和奥莱娜在那里
The only thing is that nadiya and olena are there.
他们不能离开
They can't leave.
所以我去那里拜访他们
So I go there and visit them,
因为...他们不能去任何地方
because... They can't go anywhere.
他们不能
They can't.
我的意思是 另一方面 我需要照顾这里的事情
I mean, on the other hand i need to take care of things around here.
我需要清理
I need to clean up.
我的意思是 我现在应该做的事情
I mean, I should be doing things right now.
所以我得到了 对不起 我得走了
So, I got, I'm sorry, i got to get going.
当然 我会离开你的
Of course, I'll leave you to it.
你照顾罗马
You take care, Roman.
我当然爱你 杰克
Of course I love you, Jake.
我认为这是最好的塞缪尔和我们
I think this is best for Samuel and for us,
我真的希望对你也是最好的
and I really hope it's best for you, too.
-撒母耳在哪里?我在我姐姐的记得吗?
-Where is Samuel right now? -He's at my sister's, remember?
什么 我甚至不能跟他说再见
What, I can't even say goodbye to him?
亲爱的 你不必说再见
Honey, you don't have to say goodbye.
你可以随时看到他
You can see him whenever you want.
你不必说再见
You don't have to say goodbye.
你对他说了什么?你告诉他什么?
What did you say to him? What did you tell him?
我只是告诉他我们要花了
I just told him we were gonna spend
在阿姨的家里几夜 -克里斯蒂娜
-a few nights at his aunt's house. -Christina.
你知道 他爱狗和猫
You know, he loves having the dog and the cats around.
他不会明白的
He's not gonna understand that.
他现在不会 但最终他会的
He will, not right now, but he will eventually.
我们会让他正常
We'll just make it normal for him.
杰克 我想你只需要一些时间专注于你
Jake, I think you just need some time to focus on you.
因为如果我们继续这样生活 我想我们会保持
Because if we keep living like this I think we'll just keep
伤害彼此 你知道
hurting each other and, you know,
我们会得到一个点 我不知道我们是否可以解决它
we'll get to a point where i don't know if we can fix it.
所以我们要为撒母耳这样做
So we're gonna do this for Samuel.
对我们来说
And for us.
好的?
Okay?
对 撒母耳记上
Yeah, for Samuel.
那就是斯普林菲尔德军械库
That's the Springfield armory.
十一加一回合$ 674
Eleven plus one rounds, $674.
三 两英寸贝雷塔斯
Three, two-inch berettas,
十加一回合 会跑你约570美元
ten plus one rounds, will run you about $570.
现在 我们拥有的两个史密斯和威森模型 黑色的m＆p
Now, the two Smith & Wesson models we have, the black m&p,
八加一回合 将会运行约560美元
eight plus one rounds, will run you about $560
和空气38特别 它有更多的经典的空气
and the airweight 38 special, it's got more of a classic air
和不锈钢表面处理
and a stainless steel finish,
所以这会让你约$ 436
so that's gonna run you about $436.
我们最便宜的型号
Our cheapest model
是高点9毫米 $ 199
is the hi point 9 millimeter, $199.
配有一把免费的小刀
Comes with a free pocket knife.
邦诺斯先生 我们可以跟你说话吗?
Mr. bonanos, can we speak with you for a moment?!
杰克
Jake.
杰克怎么样?
How you doing, Jake?
我很好谢谢
I'm fine, thanks.
如果你们有好的 我想直截了当地说
If it's okay with you guys, I'd like to get straight to the point,
我不想再等你了
I don't wanna keep you waiting any longer.
好 当然
Yeah, sure.
所以我们还没有试用日期
So we still don't have a trial date.
这将需要一段时间 但你知道管理层会提供
That will take a while but you know management will provide
所有您需要的法律保障 所以
all the legal coverage you need, so.
我们在想你 杰克
We're thinking of you, Jake.
这是我提供的第二次
This is the second time I've offered,
但我们都同意你可以使用一些心理支持
but we all agree you could use some psychological support.
我知道克里斯蒂娜同意我们的看法
I know Christina agrees with us on that one.
对 对吧
Yeah, right.
而就工作而言 有几个选择
And as far as work goes, there are several options.
你可以留在这里做行政工作
You could stay here doing administrative work.
嗯 我不知道
Um, I don't know.
或者我们也可以为您提供另一种可能性
Or we could also offer you another possibility.
只有当你有兴趣 当然
Only if you're interested, of course,
但是我们可以为您提供的遣散费
but the severance package that we could offer you
可能非常有利
could be very advantageous.
管理层 他们总是推荐什么是最适合工作的人
Management, they always recommend what's best for the worker
但在您的具体情况下 为了保证您的安全
but in your particular case, in order to guarantee your safety,
如果您考虑进行更改 可能符合您的最佳利益
it may be in your best interest if you were to consider making a change.
一个彻底的变化 杰克
A radical change, Jake.
最安全的不仅仅是另一个工作 这是另一个城市
The safest isn't just another job, it's another city.
另一个家
Another home.
另一个名字
Another name.
另一种生活
Another life.
没关系 没关系
That's okay, that's okay.
但我的妻子在这里
But my... my wife's here.
我的...我的家人
My... my family.
我不能只是...
I can't just...
我们不能刚刚起身 你知道吗?
We can't just up and move, you know?
这可能是您和您的家人最安全的事情
This may potentially be the safest thing to do for you and your family.
你真的必须考虑我们现在给你的是什么
You really have to consider what we're presenting to you right now.
想想他们的最大利益和福祉
Think about their best interest and their well being.
好吧 当他回到你面前 让我知道
Let me know when he gets back to you, alright.
他应该已经回到我身边了
He was supposed to get back to me already.
-詹姆士 -先生梅尔尼克
-James. -Mr. melnyk.
我不认为你知道代表航空公司的律师
I don't think you know the lawyers representing the airlines,
约翰和詹姆斯gullick
John and James gullick.
我很抱歉让你等待
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
与受害者家属的会议
The meetings with the victims' families
这些日子过去了
have been carrying over these days.
没关系
That's okay.
请允许我说大多数人都非常富有成果
Allow me to say that most have been very fruitful.
正在达成协议这就是为什么我们今天在这里
Agreements are being reached. Which is why we're here today.
达成协议
To reach an agreement.
梅尔尼克先生 你是唯一选择的家庭成员
Mr. melnyk, you are the only family member who has chosen
自己起诉公司 没有律师 没有
to sue the company by himself, without a lawyer and without
与任何受害者协会签约
signing up with any of the victims' associations.
我想让你知道你有我们的完全尊重
I'd like you to know that you have our complete respect
对我们来说 没有什么区别
and that to us it makes no difference.
我们的建议将是完全一样的
Our proposal will be exactly the same.
詹姆士
James.
梅尔尼克先生 这是框架协议
Mr. melnyk, this is the framework agreement
我们向家庭提出建议
we're proposing to the families.
我想要 -
I would like to just--
这是一个友好的协议
it's a friendly agreement
在你和你同意的航空公司之间
between you and the airline in which you agree
撤回公司的所有索赔和诉讼
to withdraw all claims and lawsuits from the company.
现在 作为交换 公司将照顾你的家人
Now, in exchange, the company will take care of your family's
丧葬费和任何医疗或心理治疗
funeral expenses and any medical or psychological treatment
这可能已经被认为是必要的
that may have been deemed necessary to date.
公司还同意向您支付赔偿金额
The company also agrees to pay you damages in the amount of
您女儿死亡75,000美元 您妻子85,000美元
$75,000 for your daughter's death and $85,000 for your wife's.
-总共$ 16万 -我想要 -
-$160,000 in total. -I would like to just--
合同中还有一些小条款
there are also some minor clauses in the contract.
例如 您将自动接收高级客户端状态
For example, you will automatically receive premium client status
从我们集团内的航空公司
from the airline within our group.
您将能够受益于这些和其他优势
You'll be able to benefit from those and other advantages.
这些是您应仔细阅读的细节
These are details that you should read carefully
因为他们在合同中有明确的解释
because they are clearly explained in the contract.
我想让一个人说 他们很抱歉为了杀死我的家人
I would like for someone to say that they're sorry for killing my family.
我想让公司道歉
I want the company to apologize.
梅尔尼克先生 让我更简单地向你解释一下
Mr. melnyk, let me explain this to you a little more simply.
如果您不签合同
If you don't sign this contract,
你可能不会得到一分钱的所有这一切
you're probably not gonna get a penny for all of this.
现在 16万美元是很多钱
Now $160,000 is a lot of money.
有人在你的位置不应该拒绝这样的报价
Someone in your position shouldn't turn down such an offer.
看这张照片
Look at this photo.
因为你以前没有
Because you didn't before.
看它
Look at it.
看它！
Look at it!
你现在在想什么?
Where's your mind right now?
仍然觉得你不能
Still feel like you're unable
与你的家人接触?
to engage with your family?
仍然感到沉思?
Still feeling pensive?
那么今天我们来试试吧
Well, today let's try to focus
在这个星期的积极的感觉
on the positive feelings you've had this week.
来吧...我真的希望我可以在我的处方上获得补充
Come... I was really hoping i could just get a refill on my prescription.
在那些感到放心的时刻
On those moments when you feel at ease...
也许做一些令人满意的事情
Maybe doing something you find satisfying.
这可能看起来很愚蠢 但让你感觉很好
It may seem silly, but makes you feel good.
想想你的日常生活
Think about your daily routine.
在家里 你去的地方 你每周看到的人
At home, places you go, people you see on a weekly basis.
我真的只是想要处方
I really just want the prescription.
漫步 电视节目 与朋友交谈
A stroll, a TV program, talking to a friend.
看 我不觉得很好漫步或吃饭
Look, I don't feel good strolling or eating,
或看到任何人 或与任何人交谈
or seeing anyone, or talking to anyone.
那么请给我他妈的药
So just give me the fucking pills, please.
或者我会走在街上 抢走那个被遗弃的药店
Or I'll go down the street and rob the goddamned pharmacy.
“这些都会消除永远的惩罚
"And these will go away into eternal punishment,
而是义人进入永生“
but the righteous into eternal life."
马太所说的永生
That eternal life which Matthew spoke of,
告诉我们我们亲人的感觉是别的地方
that feeling that tells us our loved ones are somewhere else, somewhere better,
是在今天这样的一天必须盛行的感觉
is the feeling that must prevail on a day like today.
一年前 我们受到一个悲剧性的事件的打击
One year ago we were struck by a tragic event.
许多生命不公正地丧生
Many lives were lost unjustly,
不可思议和意外的
incomprehensibly and unexpectedly.
但今天我们失去的人的精神
But today the spirits of the people we lost
在别的地方 看着我们
are somewhere else, watching us.
他们可以看到 像今天这样的一天 我们记得他们 向他们致敬
And they can see that on a day like today we remember them and pay tribute to them.
为了保持这种记忆活力
And to keep this memory alive,
把它留在我们里面
to keep it ingrained inside of us,
在这个地方 今天我们开了这座纪念碑
and in this place, today we inaugurate this monument,
这个纪念碑给遇难者
this memorial to the victims.
罗马melnyk?
Roman melnyk?
我是安德鲁•伯格
I'm Andrew berg.
我在事故中失去了我的妻子和我的媳妇
I lost my wife and my in-laws in the accident.
我非常抱歉
I'm very sorry.
我在关于你女儿项链的文章中看过这个故事
I read the story in the papers about your daughter's necklace.
我以为这是很好 他们用它
I thought it was nice that they used it as
灵感为纪念碑
inspiration for the monument.
你喜欢它吗?
Do you like it?
是
Yes.
你是什么...
What do you...
我...我不知道该怎么办
I... I don't know what to do.
我早上起床 我不知道该怎么办
I get up in the morning and I don't know what to do.
也许这不是我不知道该怎么做全天
Maybe it's not that I don't know what to do the whole day,
这是我不知道在接下来的一个小时做什么
it's that I don't know what to do in the next hour
或下一分钟
or the next minute.
对不起 我很诚实
I'm sorry, I'm being so honest.
没关系
That's okay.
前进
Go ahead.
有时我试着想到的东西分散我的注意力
Sometimes I try to think of things to distract me,
你知道 只是想一想别的东西
you know, just try and think about something else,
那我立刻忘记了 我不做
then I immediately forget and I don't do them.
我只是坐在家里 不知道该怎么办
I just sit at home, not knowing what to do.
这不容易
It won't be easy,
但迟早
but sooner or later
你会发现一些东西
you will find something
这将帮助你下床
that'll help you get out of bed.
-你这么认为我知道了
-You think so? -I know so.
耐心一点
Be patient.
这就是我所需要的 而不是
That's what I need, dammit.
你有没有通过它?
Have you gotten through it?
-去过坎昆? -没有
-Ever been to Cancun? -No.
这是一个美妙的地方 在尤卡坦半岛北端
It's a wonderful place and in the northern tip of the Yucatan peninsula.
嗯 你们看起来像你感兴趣的东西吗?
Um, is that something you guys seem like you're interested in?
是啊-是啊
-Yeah. -Yeah, yeah.
好的 有一艘离开佛罗里达州的游轮
Okay, there's a cruise ship leaving out of Florida
它直接在那里
and it heads just straight down there.
让我得到你的一些信息
Let me get some of your information
我会让你们开始
I'll get you guys started.
怎么样了?
How's it going?
大
Great.
好吧 来吧 休息一下
Well, come on, time for a break.
不 今天我想完成这一点
No, I'd like to finish this side today.
我已经打开他们了
I already opened them, so.
谢谢
Thanks.
哦 这个星期的工资
Oh... this week's pay.
直到我完成
Not until I'm finished.
-你做的很好 -谢谢
-You're doing a great job. -Thanks.
如果我喜欢我妻子挑选的围栏 那将是惊人的
If I liked the fence that my wife picked out it'd be amazing.
再见 伙计们
Bye, guys.
-先生梅尔尼克我需要问你一个忙
-Mr. melnyk. -I need to ask you a favor.
我要你帮我找他
I want you to help me find him.
-Pat 它是Tessa  -我知道已经很久了
-Pat, it's Tessa. -I know it's been a long time.
我来到镇上 我们可以在哪里见面吗?
I'm coming to town, is there somewhere we could meet?
这本书已经完成了我必须在下周送出布置
The book is finished. I have to send it in next week for lay-out,
但如果你真的想说任何事情会是一种荣誉
but if you really wanted to say anything it would be an honor.
这就是为什么我不想问你什么具体的
That's why I don't wanna ask you anything specific.
我不是在谈论面试或照片
I'm not talking about an interview or photographs.
我只想给你一个机会说些什么
I just wanna give you a chance to say something.
添加评论 想法?
Add a comment, a thought?
或者根本不说什么 如果这是你想要的
Or to not say anything at all, if that's what you want.
你知道 有时我...
You know, sometimes I...
有时我把自己放在鞋子里
Sometimes I put myself in their shoes.
你知道 家庭的
You know, the families'.
然后我想到我的儿子和我的妻子
And then I think about my son and my wife,
它吓到我死亡 这太可怕了
and it scares me to death, it's terrifying.
我的意思是说我能说什么?
I mean, what can I say?
你知道吗
You know, I...
我只是想让我内心的痛苦消失
I just want this pain inside of me to go away.
所以 告诉他们
So, tell them...
看 我不是一个坏人
Look, I'm not a bad person.
对?
Right?
好的 我会看到你们的 -周一见
-Alright, I'll see you guys. -See you Monday.
有一个很好的周末 拍拍 -你也是
-Have a good weekend, pat. -You too.
-是? -我找到了他
-Yes? -- I found him.
嗨 你好
Hi.
他把他的房子出售给了另一个国家
He put his house up for sale and moved to another state.
他在一家旅行社工作 距离他的新公寓四个街区
He works at a travel agency four blocks away from his new apartment.
他的地址是什么?
And what's his address?
我不知道我应该给你吗
I don't know if I should give you that.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我希望你以正确的方式使用这些信息
I'd like you to use this information in the correct way.
没有正确的方法或不正确的方式
There is no correct way or incorrect way.
这不是那么简单
It's not that simple.
我告诉过你 我只想看着他
I told you, I just want to look him in the eye.
给他看看我家的照片
Show him a photograph of my family.
我要他道歉
I want him to apologize.
没有人说他们很抱歉没有人
No one has said they're sorry. No one.
巴特伯特
Pat dealbert.
Pat dealbert?
他的名字现在是pat dealbert
His name is pat dealbert now.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
再见
Goodbye.
帕特伯特家在家吗?
Is pat dealbert home?
他肯定是 就是我
He sure is, that's me.
我们在这里待在周末
We're here to stay the weekend.
我知道哥们 我知道
I know buddy, I know.
嗨嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
我很高兴你在这里
I'm glad you're here.
好的 让我得到你的东西
Okay, let me get your stuff.
我们正在这里排练他的线条
We were rehearsing his lines the whole way here.
好的 他做得很好
Yeah, well, he did a good job.
嘿 你们比我想象的早很多
Hey, you guys are a lot earlier than I thought.
是的 我们做得很好
Yeah, we made great time.
我们在乘客座位上有一个速度恶魔
We had a speed demon in the passenger seat.
我刚刚完成晚餐 你们自己在家里
I'm just finishing up dinner, you guys make yourselves at home.
是啊
Yeah.
那么你告诉他 你是谁呢?
So who did you tell him pat dealbert was?
我告诉他 就像克拉克肯特或布鲁斯•韦恩
I told him it was like Clark Kent or Bruce Wayne.
你告诉人的一个名字 所以他们不知道
A name you told people so they wouldn't know
你是超级英雄的真相
the truth that you're a superhero.
所以我是...我是超级杰克
So I'm... I'm super Jake.
是的 起初他说这是愚蠢的
Yeah, at first, he said it was stupid,
但是 他认为这很有趣
but, then he thought it was kind of funny.
是啊
Yeah.
而且 你感觉如何?
And, um, how have you been feeling?
老实说
Honestly?
单独
Alone.
呃...
Um...
这种整体感觉不自然
This whole kind of place feels unnatural.
你知道 我有几天醒来
You know, i have days that I wake up
我觉得事情越来越好
and I feel like things are getting better
第二天我醒来就好像是这样
and the next day I wake up it just kind of feels like
事情越来越糟
things are getting worse.
嗯 我是...我确定需要时间
Well, I'm... I'm sure it'll take time.
搬来这
Move here.
退出你的工作 搬到这里 你和塞缪尔
Quit your job and move here, you and Samuel.
是的 这是我们所有人的好地方
Yeah, this'd be a great place for all of us
得到一个新的开始
to get a fresh start.
我们都可以成为超级英雄
And we could all be super heroes.
我想我们只需要...慢点
I think we just need to... To take it slow.
你知道 我觉得好点了
You know, I think it's better.
是的 是的 当然
Yeah, yeah, of course.
嗯...我为你们做了床
Um... I made the bed for you guys
所以我今晚要睡在沙发上
so I'm gonna sleep on the sofa tonight.
什么?
What?
我只是认为这是计划
I just thought that was the plan.
我猜 嗯 我的计划是大家都可以
I guess, um, my plan was we could all
我们三个人坐在一张床上
fit in one bed, the three of us.
好的 那么我的计划不再是我的计划
Okay, well, then my plan is no longer my plan.
好
Good.
杰克
Jake.
你好?
Hello?
我喜欢它
I love it.
妈妈
Mama.
我喜欢它
I love it.
我认为这一切都取决于这张卡哦 等等 不 不
I think it all depends on this card. Oh, wait, no, no.
我得到了我们好工作 伙计
-He got us. -Good job, buddy.
我赢了
I win.
-好的 -再玩一次
-Alright. -Let's play again.
-再次? -现在迟到了
-Again? -Honey, it's late.
请?
Please?
好吧 这将是一个非常快的游戏 好吗?
Alright, it'll be a really quick game, okay?
-是我会填补这些
-Yes. -I'm gonna fill these up.
你知道吗?当你爸爸这样做的时候 睡衣
You know what? While your dad's doing that, pajamas.
-好的哦 要刷牙
-Okay. -Okay, brush some teeth.
是?
Yes?
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
看这张照片
Look at this photo.
这是我的家人！
This is my family!
听我说你不能像这样听到我在这里出现吗?
Listen to me. You can't be showing up here like this you hear me?
-看它！ -我看到了 但我的家人在这里 好吗?
-Look at it! -I see it, but my family's here, okay?
你杀了他们！如果你不离开 我会打电话给警察局
-You killed them! -I'm gonna call the police if you don't leave.
我的儿子在这里！没有人道歉！
-My son is in here! -No one had apologized!
你杀了他们！这是一个意外 好吗?
-You killed them! -It was an accident, okay?!
你听到我吗?你有什么事?
You hear me?! What's the matter with you?!
你不能像这样出现你失去了什么?
You can't be showing up like this. What have you lost your mind?
我现在打电话给警察 你需要离开！
I'm gonna call the police right now, you need to leave!
你懂我的?你需要离开！
You understand me? You need to leave!
这是一个意外我没有杀死任何人！
It was an accident. I didn't kill anybody!
什么到你身上你现在要离开了！
What's gotten into you? You need to leave now!
你疯了吗?
Have you lost your mind?
你现在要离开了 或者我打电话给警察局
You need to leave now or I'm gonna call the police.
你听到我吗你听到我吗
You hear me? You hear me?
待在这
Stay here.
奥莉娜 留下来
Olena, stay back.
留下来
Stay back.
妈妈?
Mommy?
纳迪亚
Nadiya.
不要害怕
Don't be afraid.
不要害怕 纳迪亚
Don't be afraid, nadiya.
没有
No.
他不知道 新生活
He did not know  that the new life
不会给他什么
would not be given to him for nothing,
他必须付出昂贵的代价
that he would have to pay dearly for it,
这将使他付出巨大的冲突和巨大的痛苦
that it would cost him great strife and great suffering.
但是 那就是一个新故事的开始
But that, that is the beginning of a new story.
一个人的更新的故事
The story of the renewal of a man,
他的渐进再现的故事
the story of his gradual regeneration,
他从一个世界传入另一个世界
of his passing from one world into another.
罗马 我们走吧
Roman, let's go.
所以他们同意 审查句子
So they agreed  to review the sentence
并应用我们提出的减轻我们的情况
and apply the extenuating circumstances we presented.
说实话 罗马啊
And to be honest, Roman, ah,
我没想到他们会大大减少这句话
I didn't expect them to reduce the sentence so drastically.
已经十年了 你可以在四个月内获得假释
It's been ten years and you could get parole in four months.
你每周必须拜访精神科医生三次
You'll have to visit a psychiatrist three times a week,
谁会写出你的进度的每月报告
who will write up monthly reports on your progress.
如果你去每一个会议和这些报告是积极的
If you go to every session and those reports are positive,
你可能不必再回到监狱 罗马
you might not have to go back to prison, Roman.
嗨 你好
Hi.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
哦对不起我是 我正在寻找退出 我想我迷路了
Oh, sorry. I'm, I'm looking for the exit, I think I'm lost.
就在那边
It's right over there.
你需要转几圈
You need to make a couple of turns.
-我会带你的-你确定?
-Come, I'll take you. -You sure?
是的 我正朝着这个方向前进
Yeah, I'm heading that way anyway, come.
谢谢
Thank you.
是的 我从来没有去过这里
Yeah, I've never been here before.
哦 上次我在这里是11年前
Oh, last time I was here was 11 years ago.
长时间
Long time.
一切都完全一样
Everything is exactly the same.
自从我第一次来以后 没有任何改变
Nothing has changed since the first time I came.
同样的树木 同样的百里香味
The same trees, the same smell of thyme.
所有的东西不 那不是百里香
-Same everything. -No, that isn't thyme.
-它的美味 -哦耶?
-It's savory. -Oh, yeah?
气味像百里香给我
Smells like thyme to me.
但它不是
But it isn't.
你有家庭成员吗?
You have family members here?
没有
No.
我父亲没有埋葬在这里
My father isn't buried here.
你知道 当我跟着你时
You know, when I was following you,
我不知道什么时候接近你
I didn't know exactly when to approach you,
哪里是最好的地方
where'd be the best place.
但是 当我看到你今天早晨乘坐那辆公共汽车
But when I saw you get on that bus this morning
我意识到你来到这里我想
and I realized you were coming here I thought,
这是完美的结局
the perfect place for this to end.
等待
Wait.
回转
Turn around.
回转！
Turn around!
前进
Go ahead.
做你要做的事情
Do what you have to do.
我明白
I understand.
但是我想让你知道 对不起
But I want you to know that, I'm sorry.
对于我所做的 我很抱歉
I'm sorry for what I did.
我可以做到
I could do it.
但我不会去
But I'm not going to.
这不是我所教的
It's not what I was taught.
你会去吗?
Will you just go, please?
好的
Okay.
本字幕由随缘字幕组修订制作 欢迎加群374282202一起看片◑ω◑